schemaapp.com 2019-12-07

# Privacy Policy - Schema App Tools

[Schema App](https://www.schemaapp.com/) is a service offered by the business [Hunch Manifest Inc](https://www.hunchmanifest.com/).

Your privacy is important to us and we encourage you to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices set forth herein.

By accessing or otherwise using the website operated or any applications operated by Hunch Manifest Inc., you agree to be bound contractually by this Privacy Policy.  Hunch Manifest Inc. (also referred to as “Schema App”, “we”, “us” and “our”) operates the website.  This Privacy Policy applies to information collected, used and maintained by us in conjunction with the use of our services, applications and website. The following explains our information gathering and dissemination practices.

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their **‘Personally Identifiable Information’** (PII) is being used online. PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

#### The Right to Modify

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time by posting amended terms on the Website or otherwise notifying you of changes to this Privacy Policy. Your continued use after such amendment following the Effective Date indicates your acceptance of the amended Privacy Policy. You should check this Privacy Policy periodically for modifications by referencing the Effective Date posted above. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all Personally Identifiable Information that we have about you. However, we will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of personally identifiable information collected in the past without the consent of affected users.

#### What personal information do we collect from people that register on Schema App?

When purchasing or registering on our site, as appropriate, you are required to supply personal data, including your name, email address, phone number, business name to help you with your experience. 

#### When do we collect information?

We collect information from you when you register for Schema App, purchase a product on our site (plugin, app, training, etc), subscribe to a newsletter or enter information into web forms.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  * To quickly process your transactions.
  * To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products
  * To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

We also collect and use information about your use, and the use by other customers, of the Services in order to improve and enhance the Services, to repair errors or bugs, and to develop new versions of the product.

#### What are your rights?

You have the right to access and edit your Account and Profile Information (including User ID and billing details) by logging into the Services and choosing to edit your Profile. You are able to upgrade, downgrade, and cancel your Subscription, enable, download a text file of your Account Data, and invite additional Users to your Account (depending on your Account level).

Under the GDPR, you may be entitled to additional rights, including: (i) the right to withdraw consent to processing where consent is the basis of processing; (ii) the right to access your Personal Data and certain other supplementary information, under certain conditions; (iii) the right to object to unlawful data processing, under certain conditions; (iv) the right to erasure of Personal Data about you, under certain conditions; (v) the right to demand that we restrict processing of your Personal Data, under certain conditions, if you believe we have exceeded the legitimate basis for processing, processing is no longer necessary, are processing, or believe your Personal Data is inaccurate; (vi) the right to data portability of Personal Data concerning you that you provided us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format, under certain conditions; (vii) the right object to decisions being taken by automated means which produce legal effects concerning you or similarly significantly affect you, under certain conditions; (viii) the right to lodge a complaint with data protection authorities. If you want to learn more about your rights under the GDPR, you can visit the European Commission’s page on Data Protection at: <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/index_en.htm>. We will maintain your Personal Data for as long as they are needed, or as required by applicable laws, regulations, or government orders. Unless you request otherwise, your Account, including Schema Data, will be deleted from our databases within twelve (12) months of Account cancellation. We reserve the right to charge a fee for data retention past our prescribed deletion period, and to update or amend our data retention policy.

While Schema App is a Canadian company, we work with companies and users around the world, including in the European Economic Area. As part of our service, we may transfer your personal information to other regions, including to Canada and the United States.

#### How do we protect your information?

**Account Information** : When you sign up for a Schema App Account, you select a User ID (by entering an email address and password) and we collect and store that information. Collected information is data we have solicited in a form or obtained via cookies or by other means; stored information is collected information that has been subsequently deposited into our databases after collection. In addition to your User ID, we also collect and store your first name and last name. We may also collect and store your company name, telephone number, address, and certain other information about you that may be required by us to provide the Services or be disclosed by you during your use of the Services.

**Billing Information:** When your Account includes a Subscription, we collect, but do not store, your credit card number. We do collect and store your billing address. Full credit card numbers are never visible to Schema App employees or contractors, and we will not modify your credit card number or billing address under any circumstances. We adhere to all controls required for handling cardholder data in accordance with Payment Card Industry (PCI) compliance standards. You agree that our Third Party payment processors may collect and store your billing address and credit card information on our behalf. We are not responsible or liable for the ways in which Third Parties collect, store, or process your Personal Information or Sensitive Information, or other details about you.

**Log Data:** When you use our Services, our servers may automatically collect and store information, including information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include, but is not limited to, your Internet Protocol (IP) address, the address of the web page you visited before using the Services, the operating system you are using, the date and time of your accessing the Services, geolocation information, type of device, cookie data, and browser signatures.

  * IP Addresses: We will log the IP address of any visitor to a webpage you create and publish using the Services in order to calculate traffic usage per Account and conversion rates per variant, investigate spam allegations and discrepancies in page statistics, as well as to ensure the security of the webpage, Services, and related data. Schema App never uses the IP address or other Personal Information of visitors to your pages to conduct marketing activities or promote the Services.
  * Cookies and Log Files: Cookies are small amounts of data that are transferred to your web browser by a web server and are used to collect and store information about a user. The ways we use cookies include, but are not limited to: tracking which webpage variant a visitor has seen, monitoring traffic patterns, and gauging the popularity of service options. Cookies also allow us to ensure that visitors see the webpage variant they expect to see if they return to the same website URL, and to calculate total visits and views per webpage, variant, Account, and client sub-account.  Use of the Site and Services signifies consent to Schema App’s use of cookies, including and without limitation Third Party cookies that Schema App may choose to use for analytics or other purposes. You agree that should you disable cookies on your browser, certain aspects of the Services may be unavailable to you, and that Schema App is not responsible for any adverse effects arising from your browser or other computer or mobile settings.
  * You agree that you are responsible for adhering to all laws, policies, and other regulations in your relevant jurisdiction(s), including but not limited to all laws requiring that cookie use must be disclosed. Schema App disclaims all liability in this area.

#### Third-party disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it’s release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Where permitted by law, we may share information from or about you with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or other companies under common control, in which case we will require them to honour this Privacy Policy.

If we are acquired by or merged with another entity, if substantially all of our assets are transferred to another company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected about you to the other company. Our successors and assigns may collect and use your information for substantially similar purposes as described in this Privacy Policy

#### Third-party links

Our Websites may contain hyperlinks to websites of third parties (“ **Third Party Websites** ”) that can cause you to leave the website currently being browsed by the User. We provide these hyperlinks for convenience. The Third Party Websites are not under our control, therefore we have no control over the privacy and confidentiality practices of such Third Party Websites. Accordingly, any Personal Information that is transmitted by use of Third Party Websites is subject to the privacy policy of the relevant Third Party Websites. It is the responsibility of the Users to consult these policies in order to ensure that their Personal Information is being protected.

We may use social media (for example, Facebook and Twitter) in addition to the operation of the Website. Social media accounts are public and are not hosted by us. The Users who decide to interact with us through social media must, therefore, read the terms of service and privacy policies of these third-party suppliers of services and the applications used to have access to them.

The Personal Information that is provided to us by way of social media accounts is collected in order to record exchanges (for example, questions and answers, comments, “likes”, shared tweets) between the User and us. It may be used to answer requests, make statistical evaluations and to prepare reports and for all other purposes indicated in this Policy.

#### Google

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548>

We use Google Analytics, YouTube, and AdWords for our site. 

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

**We have implemented the following:**

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * Facebook Tracking Pixel

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

#### Third Party Behavioral Tracking

We do not allow third-party behavioral tracking.

#### Fair Information Practices

In correspondence with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur, we will notify the users via in-site notification within 7 business days. We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

#### CAN SPAM Act

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or  questions
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * Send  you additional information related to your product and/or service
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  * Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

#### Security

We will strive to prevent unauthorized access to your Personal Data, however, no data transmission over the Internet, by wireless device or over the air is guaranteed to be 100% secure. We will continue to enhance security procedures as new technologies and procedures become available.

We strongly recommend that you choose a strong, unguessable password, and that you do not disclose your password to anyone. If you forget your password, we will ask you for your email address and send you an email with instructions for resetting your password. At no time is an Unbounce employee able to view your password.

Please remember that you control what Personal Data you provide while using the Site and Services. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your identification, passwords and/or any Personal Data in your possession for the use of the Site and/or Services. Always be careful and responsible regarding your Personal Data. We are not responsible for, and cannot control, the use by others of any information which you provide to them and you should use caution in selecting the Personal Data you provide to others through the Site or Services. Similarly, we cannot assume any responsibility for the content of any Personal Data or other information which you receive from other users through the Site or Services, and you release us from any and all liability in connection with the contents of any Personal Data or other information which you may receive using the Site or Services. We cannot guarantee, or assume any responsibility for verifying, the accuracy of the Personal Data or other information provided by any Third Party. You release us from any and all liability in connection with the use of such Personal Data or other information of others.

#### Children’s Privacy

The Site and/or Services are not directed to children under the age of 16, and we do not knowingly collect Personal Data from children under the age of 16 without obtaining parental consent. If you are under 16 years of age, then please do not use or access the Site and/or Services at any time or in any manner. If we learn that Personal Data has been collected on the Site and/or Services from persons under 16 years of age and without verifiable parental consent, then we will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. If you are a parent or guardian and discover that your child under 16 years of age has provided Personal Data, then you may alert us as set forth in the “Contact Us” section and request that we delete that child’s Personal Data from our systems.

#### Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or your Personal Data, to make an access or correction request, to exercise any applicable rights, to make a complaint, or to obtain information about our policies and practices with respect to any service providers outside the EU/EEA, we can be reached by email: [support@schemaapp.com](mailto:support@schemaapp.com).

_Updated: Feb 12th, 2019_
